<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Ömer Mindivanli Blog]]></title><description><![CDATA[A starter blog demonstrating what Ömer's ideas are]]></description><link>https://omermindivanli.com</link><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 19:30:25 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[What is goin' on my life...]]></title><description><![CDATA[I just wanna talk about somethings I currently think Hi Everyone, Just a couple of minutes ago, the computer has been given by Tieto, which…]]></description><link>https://omermindivanli.com/My last thoughts on what is going on my life/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://omermindivanli.com/My last thoughts on what is going on my life/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2018 00:33:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;I just wanna talk about somethings I currently think&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hi Everyone,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just a couple of minutes ago, the computer has been given by Tieto, which is current company I work, has broken down. There was a operating system error. I, therefore, tried to use my ex mac, which is pretty satisfing as a personal computer, and then, I wanted to write something on my blog.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You know I have started on my new job in Sweden. I am pretty satisfied with my job, workplace and team. They are quite nice people. Especially, in Sweden, People have a great respect to one another, which makes us feel like we work in job security. I strongly believe that there are millions of people are on the trouble of job security. On these days, I try to TALK swedish, which is the most important thing in Sweden, I guess but, of course, is not mandotary or as important as Danish or German. I mean if you do not know Swedish ppl do not push you or something else. They always support you to speak more and more. I LOVE SWEDISH PEOPLE SÅ MYCKET ( So much :) ) Anyways, just currently started to talk Swedish slowly. It will also help me to make new friends, as well, which triggers me a lot lol haha :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As for Tieto, my managers and colleauges are very friendly, respectful, polite and supportive and also understanding. I can always demand them like Can I have a look on that feature maybe sometime? They reply yes, of course :) They do not push me to finish something.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A year ago, I have finished a back-end project. It was not node.js but I have just began to work with some back-end development stuff which is fucking exciting for me. I am really more into develop my skillset as much as I can. It makes me feel like refresh, I think. By the way, my colleauge taught me .git very well. I use it in a proper way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When it comes to life, I must confess I am a bit alone. The scandinavian lifestyle has a tonnes of useful things for people. I do not complain but it might make you maybe a tiny alone. Perhaps we can call it like individualistic. As a person who has grown up in a family-oriented society, sometimes it puts lots of pressure on me like being loneliness or somethings else… But maybe you know I am very good at finding some activities or making friends. At least I try to survive in this loneliness forest haha lol. I like Swedish people. I am sure I will learn a lot from them. In the following months, I would like to visit the U.K and some parts of Europe. I have lots of friend on the U.K. I can meet with them. That is amazing.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[First Day on My New Job...]]></title><description><![CDATA[First Day on My New Job… Fortunately, after studying for a long time on javaScript and its side technologies. I have found a nice job and…]]></description><link>https://omermindivanli.com/First Day on Tieto.../</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://omermindivanli.com/First Day on Tieto.../</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2018 13:42:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;First Day on My New Job…&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fortunately, after studying for a long time on javaScript and its side technologies. I have found a nice job and recently started today. I feel delighted. To be honest, I am like over the moon :) Hopefully, everything goes well, and then, I would be a dev, who can achieve the task that would be given by my managers…&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[About me...]]></title><description><![CDATA[Introducing me briefly… Hi Everyone, My name is Ömer Mindivanli, 29 years old and from Turkey. I had lived all my life in Turkey until I…]]></description><link>https://omermindivanli.com/Introducing Myself/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://omermindivanli.com/Introducing Myself/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2018 15:40:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Introducing me briefly…&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hi Everyone, My name is Ömer Mindivanli, 29 years old and from Turkey. I had lived all my life in Turkey until I have moved to Sweden in 2016. My family lives in Istanbul. They are so sweet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Exploring new places and meeting with new people from different cultures is an exciting oppurtunity, I think. In my homeland, There are lots of foreigners but I do not know why I had no friend from different countries. I mean I am very glad to move Sweden and trying to learn Swedish culture. I would share my opinions about the Swedish Culture and people in the following blog posts. They are great! :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Meeting with Software Development&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A couple of years ago, when I was a freshman in my bachelor, I got a course which is called The Basics of Information and Communication Technologies 101. The lecturer was named Prof.Dr Kaan ERASLAN. He graduated from METU, Department of Mining Engineering. He tried to taught us C++ with Borland Builder. Interestingly, I was super successful even tough I have any sort of experience n programming. I got everything in those lessons in just a quick revision and then, started to build some kind of real world programs on my own such as calculator and etc… I thought Oh Gosh! I have a talent on it. After that,He sensed I was quite eager to learn such things in a short time. He gave me a assistanship for those lessons. Beacuse, My classmates needed help to create or implement example programs that in the instructions during those lessons and he was the only person who could direct people on how to fix bugs or explain the things how it works. He said to me that Ömer you are gonna help your friends. I accepted that offer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the first examination, which is called visa in Turkish higher-education system, I took 100 / A++ score. Everybody was shocked. Because, the lecturer said to me that it is not a common score for my course. Eventually, in the final exam, I got 90 score. He organised a ceramony and was awareded me with a chocolate. The applauses were rising by my classmates. It was such a great honor for me and then, he added”some of your friends do not have to work their areas. They would be a developer.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But, unfortunately, The result was:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I did not listen him and started programming a couple of years later. I am super regretful :) …&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I chose to improve myself in my area which is named &lt;strong&gt;Material Science and Engineering&lt;/strong&gt; and I gratuaded from Afyon Kocatepe University as a M.Sc. as Material Scientist, and then, began to my Ph.D. However, due to some reasons, I gave up my Ph.D. Perhaps, I may keep it on some years later…&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>